ebooksbay.org 2019-07-26

# Ebooksbay

Ebooksbay is dedicated to guarding your best interests and personal data. To be able to merit your faith and confidence, we firmly follow the Privacy Policy stated below. We are aware that you are vigilant about how your personal information is processed, and shared. We want to express our appreciation for giving us your trust through respecting your privacy. By using our website, and reading the contents found herein, you abide to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have queries that are not covered in this particular material, please let us know by sending a message through the Contact Us page.

Please be informed that this Privacy Policy may be changed over time, as new services and features are added. We highly suggest that you review this page every now and then to inform yourself about the recent revisions and alterations.

**What we do with information collected**

Ebooksbay is the sole proprietor of the Website and content found herein. We do not sell or share these contents to partners and third parties. The information that you provide us are processed within the Website, and are only obtained to determine what kind of information should be sent to Users who ask for it.

Ebooksbay vows to guard your personal data through a state-of-the-art and suitable security safeguards. We do not allow any third party to access your information, or the products and services that you have purchased.

We only ask for your personal information to enhance your surfing experience on our Website. These data is collected through the Contact Us forms, Newsletters, Registration forms, and cookies that Ebooksbay and its service provider collect. These tools permits you to give suggestions, comments, and feedback regarding the Website. Ebooksbay then corresponds to you using the personal information that you have submitted.  These information are disclosed and retained as needed to better serve the Users. However, we do disclose personal data to third parties when:

  * As mandatory in obtaining the services that you have requested.
  * As required by tax authorities and law.
  * As protection against illegal activity, fraud, and for the safety of employees, customers, or property.
  * If you choose to share these personal information to a third party.

Ebooksbay may obtain non-personal information, which may be used by Ebooksbay, or shared with partners, or third parties. Please be informed that this information does not, in any way, personally recognize you. The information is obtained through the use of IP addresses, cookies, traffic data, or other numeric codes used to a track a computer’s activity.

Cookies

These are small pieces of text files that are utilized to support navigation system, store information on your PC, determine one user from another, and to enhance user browsing experience. 

Ebooksbay uses cookies for the following reasons:

  * To modify our Website based on your personal liking. It is also used to recall your log-in information, so when you come back to our Website, your personal browsing experience will be presented to you.
  * In order to identify you by the time you return to Ebooksbay. We also utilize cookies to fill out a form automatically, so the User will not need to fill out the e-mail, and name fields respectively.
  * To hasten your searches.
  * We make use of the cookies to measure usage statistics and audience size. Cookies are also used for gathering statistical data like operating system, browser type, and IP address.

**Other Website Links**

Ebooksbay may contain links to third party sites. Ebooksbay is not accountable for the privacy practices of such websites, so we recommend that you review the privacy policies of these Websites, as their privacy statements may be different from ours. 

**A Special Note About Children**

Children under 18 years of age are not allowed to access Ebooksbay. If you believe that a minor submitted his/her personal information, please Contact Us.
